<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Dax Shepherd</title>
    <link>https://thedaxshepherd.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Dax Shepherd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://thedaxshepherd.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://thedaxshepherd.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thedaxshepherd.net/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Jason Romans and I work on the Microsoft business intelligence stack.
I live in Nashville, Tennessee with my wife. I grew up in Southern California in the town of Perris.
My first computer was a Commodore 64. Since then I have been hooked on computers. I would go to the computer show at the fairgrounds to buy all the parts to build or upgrade my pc. Building my newest PC was a different experience since all I had to do was click to purchase the parts and wait for them to arrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Work</title>
      <link>https://thedaxshepherd.net/mywork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thedaxshepherd.net/mywork/</guid>
      <description>I work in a small IT shop. What this means is that I have to be self motivated to learn new skills and to apply them to projects I am working on. I had to have faith that if I built out data models using Microsoft BI that the business would see the value and benefit. A build and and they will come scenario. Lastly it means that I have to wear many hats from gathering requirements from the business to developing the best data model, to creating measures, and lastly to how the data will be presented on the canvas (whether Excel or Power BI).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://thedaxshepherd.net/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thedaxshepherd.net/resources/</guid>
      <description>This list is not an exhaustive list but I want to keep track of books, podcasts, and websites that I have found helpful.
Podcasts Raw Data by P3 AdaptiveAs soon as I hear the familiar &#34;Hello Friends&#34; it makes we feel like I am among friends discussing topics especially with how it impacts the businessSQL Data PartnersData DrivenRunAsRadioPower Query MagicKasper On BI BIFocal - Clarifying Business Intelligence Books Definitive Guide to DAX - Second Edition PowerPivot Book Master Your Data with Excel and Power BI Websites SQLBIGreat blog posts as well as video courses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
