<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Dax Shepherd</title>
    <link>https://thedaxshepherd.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Dax Shepherd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://thedaxshepherd.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://thedaxshepherd.net/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thedaxshepherd.net/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Jason Romans and I work on the Microsoft business intelligence stack.
I live in Nashville, Tennessee with my wife. I grew up in Southern California in the town of Perris.
My first computer was a Commodore 64. Since then I have been hooked on computers. I would go to the computer show at the fairgrounds to buy all the parts to build or upgrade my pc. Building my newest PC was a different experience since all I had to do was click to purchase the parts and wait for them to arrive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Work</title>
      <link>https://thedaxshepherd.net/mywork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thedaxshepherd.net/mywork/</guid>
      <description>Since I work in a small IT shop I architect out the complete solution from the ground up. From pulling data from the source systems (Payroll, Netsuite ERP, JD Edwards) into SQL Server to modeling the data in SQL Server Analysis Services to Power BI. I develop all the measures in DAX that are needed for the model.
I use SQL Server Integration Services to pull the data, store it in SQL Server 2019, build the data model using Tabular Editor with Model Auto Build (C# scripting) and deploy it to SQL Server Analysis Services 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
